Guide to the Heraldo Muñoz Papers, 1963-2013 and undated RL.00920
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2012-0111), 1972-2012
  Contains mostly unofficial correspondence and material related to work on the UN Security Council, especially in relation to Haiti, Iraq and Al Queda, to the Peacebuilding Fund, and to the Human Rights Council. Also contains material related to Chilean President Lagos, Brazil-Peru relations, and Muñoz's ambassadorship to Brazil and other international relations documents.
  - Ambassadorship to Brazil, 1996-2007 and undated (Box 15)
  - Chile-Argentina relations, 2007-2008 and undated (Box 15)
  - Chile-Bolivia relations, undated (Box 15)
  - Chile-Cuba relations, 1985-2012 (Box 15)
  - Chile-domestic, 2002-2010 (Box 15)
  - Chile-Peru relations, 2002-2009 and undated (Box 15)
  - Chile-U.S. relations, 1985-2005 and undated (Box 15)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2012 and undated (Box 15)
  - Human rights - general, 2003-2009 (Box 15)
  - International relations - general, 1998-2008 and undated (Box 15)
  - International relations - South America, undated (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 (Box 15)
  - Newspaper articles - miscellaneous, 1994, 2007 and undated (Box 15)
  - Personal/restricted, 2003-2009 and undated (Box 15)
  - Security Council reform - Heraldo Muñoz as facilitator, 2008 (Box 15)
  - United Nations, 1972-2010 and undated, 3 folders (Box 15)
- Accession (2014-0171)
  - Commission of Inquiry, 2007-2013
    Scope and Contents
    In 2009, Heraldo Muñoz was charged with investigating the assassination of former Pakistani prime minister Benizar Bhutto. This series contains Muñoz' files related to the United Nations Commission of Inquiry which investigated the assassination.
    - Correspondence, 2007-2010 (Box 16)
    - Witness Interviews Hotel, 2009 (Box 16)
    - Commission of Inquiry meeting requests (Box 16)
    - Interview Write-Ups, 2009-2010 (Box 16)
    - Extension of Mandate of Commission of Inquiry, 2009 (Box 16)
    - Appointment to Commission of Inquiry, 2009-2010 (Box 16)
    - Appointment Calendar (Box 16)
    - List of contacts/sources for COI (Box 16)
    - Comments by Pakistani Government (Box 16)
    - Press Coverage, 2009-2010 (Box 16)
    - Registration of Case, 2007-2008 (Box 16)
    - Presentation of the report of the Commission of Inquiry, 2010 (Box 16)
    - Bhutto Case: Summary of Investigation of trial conducted so far for UN Fact Finding Commission, 2009 (Box 16)
    - Commission of Inquiry - profiles for meetings, 2009 (Box 16)
    - Netherlands Forensic Institute, 2010 (Box 16)
    - UN Commission of Inquiry- meeting agendas, notes, administrative files, 2009-2010 (Box 16)
    - Background notes, 2010 (Box 16)
    - Bhutto Manuscript, 2013 (Box 16)
    - Interview report forms, 2009-2010 (Box 16)